Usage: pretext [OPTIONS] COMMAND [ARGS]...

  Command line tools for quickly creating, authoring, and building PreTeXt
  projects.

  PreTeXt Guide for authors and publishers:

  - https://pretextbook.org/documentation.html

  PreTeXt CLI README for developers:

  - https://github.com/PreTeXtBook/pretext-cli/

  Use the `--help` option on any CLI command to learn more, for example,
  `pretext build --help`.

Options:
  -v, --verbosity LVL  Sets the severity of log messaging: DEBUG for all, INFO
                       (default) for most, then WARNING, ERROR, and CRITICAL
                       for decreasing verbosity.
  --version            Show the version and exit.
  -t, --targets        Display list of build/view "targets" available in the
                       project manifest.
  -h, --help           Show this message and exit.

Commands:
  build      Build specified target
  deploy     Deploys Git-managed project to GitHub Pages.
  devscript  Alias for the developer pretext/pretext script.
  generate   Generate specified assets for default target or targets specified
             by `-t`
  import     Experimental: convert a latex file to pretext
  init       Generates/updates CLI-specific files for the current version of
             PreTeXt-CLI.
  new        Generates all the necessary files for a new PreTeXt project.
  support    Use when communicating with PreTeXt support.
  update     Update the current project to match the installed version of
             PreTeXt.  Note: to upgrade the installed version of pretext, use
             `pretext upgrade`.
  upgrade    Upgrade PreTeXt-CLI to the latest version using pip.
  view       Preview specified target based on its format.
